masscomedia.com 2015-12-19

# Best institute mass communication, Journalism, TV production, Direction, film making, broadcast jourrnalism, short film making, tv direction course - Founder Divesh Nath

**Privacy Policy** ** **

_MassCoMedia.com_  is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this website, then you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement.  
_Masscomedia.com_  may change this policy from time to time by updating this page. You should check this page from time to time to be aware of these changes. 

**We may collect the following information from you:**  
Name and job title  
Contact information including email address  
Demographic information such as postcode, preferences and interests  
Other information relevant to customer surveys and/or offers.

**What we do with the information we gather**  
We require this information to understand your needs and provide you with a better service, as well as for internal record keeping.  
We may use the information to improve our  services.  
We may periodically send promotional emails about new products, special offers or other information which we think you may find interesting using the email address which you have provided.  
From time to time, we may also use your information to contact you for market research purposes. We may contact you by email, phone, fax or mail. We may use the information to customize the website according to your interests.

**Security**  
We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorised access or disclosure, we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.

**How we use cookies**  
A cookie is a small file which asks permission to be placed on your computer's hard drive. Once you agree, the file is added and the cookie helps analyse web traffic or lets you know when you visit a particular site. Cookies allow web applications to respond to you as an individual. The web application can tailor its operations to your needs, likes and dislikes by gathering and remembering information about your preferences.  
We use traffic log cookies to identify which pages are being used. This helps us analyse data about webpage traffic and improve our website in order to tailor it to customer needs. We only use this information for statistical analysis purposes and then the data is removed from the system.  
Overall, cookies help us provide you with a better website by enabling us to monitor which pages you find useful and which you do not. A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any information about you, other than the data you choose to share with us.

**Controlling your personal information**  
You may choose to restrict the collection or use of your personal information in the following ways:  
Whenever you are asked to fill in a form on the website, look for the box that you can click to indicate that you do not want the information to be used by anybody for direct marketing purposes.

If you have previously agreed to us using your personal information for direct marketing purposes, you may change your mind at any time by writing to or emailing us.   
We will not sell, distribute or lease your personal information to third parties unless we have your permission or are required by law to do so. We may use your personal information to send you promotional information about third parties which we think you may find interesting if you tell us that you wish this to happen.  
You may request details of personal information which we hold about you under the Data Protection Act 1998. If you would like a copy of the information held on you please write to us.

If you believe that any information we are holding on you is incorrect or incomplete, please write to or email us as soon as possible. We will promptly correct any information.

**Use of Your Information**  
The information that we collect and store relating to you is primarily used to enable us to provide our services to you. In addition, we may use the information for the following purposes:  
To provide you with information requested from us, relating to our products or services. To provide information on other products which we feel may be of interest to you, where you have consented to receive such information.

**To meet our contractual commitments to you**  
To notify you about any changes to our website, such as improvements or service/product changes, that may affect our service.  
If you are an existing customer, we may contact you with information about goods and services similar to those which were the subject of a previous sale to you.  
Further, we may use your data so that you can be provided with information about unrelated goods and services which we consider may be of interest to you. We may contact you about these goods and services by any of the methods that you consented at the time your information was collected.  
If you are a new customer, we will only contact you or allow third parties to contact you only when you have provided consent and only by those means you provided consent for.  
If you do not want us to use your data for our or third parties you will have the opportunity to withhold your consent to this when you provide your details to us on the form on which we collect your data.  
Please be advised that we do not reveal information about identifiable individuals to our advertisers but we may, on occasion, provide them with aggregate statistical information about our visitors.

**Storing Your Personal Data**  
Data that are provided to us are stored on our secure servers. Details relating to any transactions entered into on our site will be encrypted to ensure its safety.

**Disclosing Your Information**  
Where applicable, we may disclose your personal information to any member of our group. This includes, where applicable, our subsidiaries, our holding company and its other subsidiaries (if any).  
We may also disclose your personal information to third parties:  
Where we sell any or all of our business and/or our assets to a third party.  
Where we are legally required to disclose your information.  
To assist fraud protection and minimise credit risk.  
**Links to other websites**  
Our website contains links to other websites of interest. These websites should have their own privacy policies which you should check. We do not accept any responsibility or liability for their policies whatsoever as we have no control over them. Once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.

**Access to Information**  
Should you wish to receive details that we hold about you please contact us using the contact details below.  
**Contacting Us**  
We welcome any queries, comments or requests you may have regarding this Privacy Policy. Please do not hesitate to contact us at [Your email address and postal address if considered appropriate].

## Some Projects Done By MassCoMedia Students

## Gallery
